<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Guide</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="version">Version</string>
    <string name="build">Build</string>
    <string name="build_date">Build Date</string>
    <string name="developers">Developers</string>
    <string name="developers_names"><![CDATA[Colin Ries & Emmanuel Braz]]></string>
    <string name="copyright">Copyright</string>
    <string name="copyright_label">© Colin Ries, Emmanuel Braz 2016</string>
    <string name="nav_intro">Intro</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="support">Support</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="items">Items</string>
    <string name="how_tos">How-Tos</string>
    <string name="header">Header</string>
    <string name="ingress_guide">Ingress Guide</string>
    <string name="subheader">by @RieCo432 and @Twiistex</string>
    <string name="sample_header">Header</string>
    <string name="sample_subheader">Subheader</string>
    <string name="badge">Badge</string>
    <string name="resonators">Resonators</string>
    <string name="xmps">XMPs</string>
    <string name="ultrastrikes">Ultra Strikes</string>
    <string name="adarefactor">ADA Refactor</string>
    <string name="jarvisvirus">Jarvis Virus</string>
    <string name="shields">Shields</string>
    <string name="axashields">AXA Shields</string>
    <string name="heatsinks">Heat Sinks</string>
    <string name="multihacks">Multi Hacks</string>
    <string name="forceamps">Force AMPs</string>
    <string name="turrets">Turrets</string>
    <string name="linkamps">Link AMPs</string>
    <string name="softbankultralinkamps">Softbank Ultra Link AMPs</string>
    <string name="powercubes">Power Cubes</string>
    <string name="capsules">Capsules</string>
    <string name="mufgcapsules">MUFG Capsules</string>
    <string name="fracker">Fracker</string>
    <string name="keylocker">Key Locker</string>
    <string name="beacons">Beacons</string>
    <string name="main">Main</string>
    <string name="badges">Badges</string>
    <string name="title_activity_item">Items IQ</string>
    <string name="portalkey">Portal Key</string>
    <string name="title_activity_badges">Badges IQ</string>

    <string name="ada">ADA</string>
    <string name="builder">Builder</string>
    <string name="connector">Connector</string>
    <string name="engineer">Engineer</string>
    <string name="explorer">Explorer</string>
    <string name="hacker">Hacker</string>
    <string name="illuminator">Illuminator</string>
    <string name="liberator">Liberator</string>
    <string name="mindcontroller">Mind Controller</string>
    <string name="purifier">Purifier</string>
    <string name="recharger">Recharger</string>
    <string name="recursion">Recursion</string>
    <string name="sojourner">Sojourner</string>
    <string name="specops">SpecOps</string>
    <string name="translator">Translator</string>
    <string name="trekker">Trekker</string>

    <string name="portalsimulator">Portal Simulator</string>
    <string name="portalsim">Portal Sim</string>
    <string name="select_resonators">Select Resonators</string>
    <string name="select_mods">Select Mods</string>
    <string name="select_links">Links</string>
    <string name="portalData">Portal Data</string>
    <string name="level">Level</string>
    <string name="range">Range</string>
    <string name="hackSpeed">Hack Speed</string>
    <string name="portalBurnoutInsulation">Burnout Insulation</string>
    <string name="portalMitigation">Mitigation</string>
    <string name="deploy">Deploy</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="item_variations_level">Levels 1 – 8</string>
    <string name="item_variations_rarity_common">-Common</string>
    <string name="item_variations_rarity_rare">-Rare</string>
    <string name="item_variations_rarity_veryrare">-Very Rare</string>
    <string name="item_variations_rarity_rare_veryrare">-Rare\n-Very Rare</string>
    <string name="item_variations_rarity_all">-Common\n-Rare\n-Very Rare</string>
    <string name="item_variations">Variations:</string>
    <string name="xmp">Exotic Matter Pulse Burster</string>
    <string name="item_notes">Notes:</string>
    <string name="item_full_name">Full Name:</string>
    <string name="item_description">Description:</string>
    <string name="item_acquisition">Acquisition:</string>
    <string name="item_intro_header">About Items in Ingress</string>
    <string name="item_acquisition_full">-via hacking\n-via passcodes</string>
    <string name="item_acquisition_hacking_only">-via Hacking</string>
    <string name="item_acquisition_passcodes_only">-via Passcodes</string>
    <string name="item_acquisition_store_only">-via the Ingress Store</string>
    <string name="item_image">Image:</string>
    <string name="portalAttackFrequency">Attack Frequency</string>
    <string name="portalOutgoingLinks">Outgoing Links</string>
    <string name="portalForce">Force</string>
    <string name="energy">Energy</string>

    <string name="resonator_description">Resonators are deployed on a portal in order to capture it or upgrade existing resonators.</string>
    <string name="resonator_notes">There\'s a limit of resonators of one level a player can deploy on one portal:\n1x L8\n1x L7\n2x L6\n2x L5\n4x L4\n4x L3\n4x L2\n8x L1</string>
    <string name="xmp_description">XMPs are weapons used to attack enemy portals. XMP\'s from different levels have different ranges of attack and higher potential damage.</string>
    <string name="xmp_notes">They are easy to hack but easy to waste. If you want to lower the number of XMPs you need to take down a portal, make sure you are as close as possible to the portal and long press the Fire button to get up to 20% attack bonus.</string>
    <string name="ultrastrike_description">Contrary to XMPs, Ultra Strikes do more damage but in a much tinier range. That\'s why they are used to destroy shields (by staying the nearest to the middle of a portal) or to destroy single resonators by staying on them as well.</string>
    <string name="ultrastrike_notes">Don\'t waste them, they are not that common in hacks. In order to get more out of an ultra strike, long press the fire button to get up to 20% attack bonus.</string>
    <string name="ada_description">An ADA Refactor is a weapon used to instantly switch the colour of a green portal to blue. Once applied on a portal, mods and resonators stay the same, but the name and the faction of the portal changes and links are being destroyed.</string>
    <string name="ada_notes">Don\'t waste them. You don\'t get AP for destroying resonators, links or fields when using an ADA. Be aware that you can only use an ADA on a portal that\'s maximal one level above your own level.</string>
    <string name="jarvis_description">A Jarvis Virus is a weapon used to instantly switch the colour of a blue portal to green. Once applied on a portal, mods and resonators stay the same, but the name and the faction of the portal changes and links are being destroyed.</string>
    <string name="jarvis_notes">Don\'t waste them. You don\'t get AP for destroying resonators, links or fields when using a Jarvis virus. Be aware that you can only use a Jarvis on a portal that\'s maximal one level above your own level.</string>
    <string name="powercubes_description">Power Cubes are used to refill your XM bar, so you can continue playing without having to pick up XM from the ground.</string>
    <string name="powercubes_notes">XM gain is calculated by multiplying the level of the power cube by 1000.</string>
    <string name="portalkey_description">Portal keys are the most important gain of a hack. With portal keys, you are able to link a portal to another portal if you\'re in the range of the start portal and if you have a key of the target portal. In addition, portal keys can be used to recharge portals when they\'re not in your range.</string>
    <string name="portalkey_notes">Once you\'ve hacked a key out of a portal, you won\'t be able to hack another one unless you drop the key or store it in a capsule of whatever type.</string>
    <string name="shields_description">Shields are a portal\'s bodyguards. They decrease the damage an XMP or Ultra Strike can do on your portal. Two attributes define a shield\'s behavior: Mitigation and Stickiness. Mitigation is the shield\'s protecting ability. The stickiness describes the shield\'s lasting ability, so to say whether it lasts long or not long when under XMP attacks.</string>
    <string name="shield_notes">Not only shields add mitigation to a portal, but links do as well. Check out our Portal Simulator for further information.</string>
    <string name="axashield_notes">The drop rate of AXA shields is slightly higher on AXA portals, which are present at all AXA agencies in some countries.</string>
    <string name="axashield_description">AXA shields are the best shields in Ingress. They have the highest mitigation and stickiness. As you might guess, they have been introduced in cooperation with the AXA assurance company.</string>
    <string name="heatsink_description">Heatsinks are mods used to decrease the waiting time between 2 hacks on the same portal. The standard amount of waiting time is 5 minutes but with heat sinks you can decrease this time to even lower than 30 seconds! See our Portal Simulator for further information.</string>
    <string name="heatsink_notes">The effect a heat sink has on portal cooldown decreases with each additional heat sink. See our Portal Simulator for quick and precise calculation of the cooldown period.</string>
    <string name="multihack_description">A multihack is used to increase the maximum amount of hacks that can be done in 4 hours (after the first hack). A standard portal can be hacked up to 4 times. Take a look at our Portal Simulator to experiment with multihack-effects.</string>
    <string name="multihack_notes">Portal burned out but you don\'t want to wait 4 hours to hack again? See if there is an empty mod slot and put in a multihack to reset the 4 hour period.</string>
    <string name="forceamp_description">Force AMPs are mods used to give a portal the power to answer with more damage by attacking an enemy player when he hacks or attacks a portal. See our Portal Simulator to find out more.</string>
    <string name="forceamp_notes">The effect of Force AMPs decreases the more you deploy, take a look at our Portal Simulator.</string>
    <string name="turret_description">Turrets are used to increase the frequency of a portal\'s attacks against enemy players, for both, XMP attacks or just hacks. For example a portal does not always shoot back when you hack or attack it, but with the turrets, you can change this probability.</string>
    <string name="turret_notes">The effect a turret has on the attack frequency decreases the more you deploy, use our Portal Simulator to calculate the attack frequency.</string>
    <string name="linkamp_description">Link AMPs are mods used to increase the maximum link range of a portal.</string>
    <string name="linkamp_notes">Very rare link amps can only be received by redeeming a passcode. They are mostly distributed on anomalies or to players who have a big and completely planned operation, when they ask Niantic.</string>
    <string name="softbankultralinkamp_description">Softbank Ultra Link Amps have many features. They increase the link range of a portal, the limit of 8 outbound link by 8 per Softbank Ultra Link and they the mitigation from links by 50%.</string>
    <string name="softbankultralinkamp_notes">Just as normal link amps, their effect decreases the more you deploy, use our Portal Simulator to calculate their effect on the portal.</string>
    <string name="capsule_description">You can store any item in capsules (except capsules…) but they won\'t free up space in your inventory.</string>
    <string name="capsule_notes">Items in a capsule still count towards the 2000 item limit of your inventory. Be aware that keys stored in a capsule cannot be used to link or recharge portals.</string>
    <string name="mufgcapsules_description">MUFG capsules are awesome, period. They have made getting very rare items much easier, due to the fact that they duplicate items after a certain time that you\'ve them in.</string>
    <string name="mufgcapsule_notes">Items in a MUFG capsule still count towards inventory item limit. In order to make items duplicate, the capsule must have some free slots and your inventory must as well have a few free slots.</string>
    <string name="fracker_description">Frackers are powerups which can be bought in the Store in Ingress. When used on a Portal, they double the hack output for 10 minutes or for 150 hacks, whatever comes first.</string>
    <string name="fracker_notes">Best way to use them is when there are several rare or very rare heatsinks on the portal and when more than 1 or 2 players take advantage of it. Just like any other buyable item, they cannot be dropped or recycled.</string>
    <string name="keylocker_description">Keylockers are similar to capsules. However, Keylockers can only store keys but they don\'t count towards the inventory item limit. They can be bought in the Ingress Store.</string>
    <string name="keylocker_notes">Just like any other buyable item, they cannot be dropped or recycled.</string>
    <string name="beacon_description">Beacons are simple markers on the scanner that hover over a portal. For some they are more a fun item than a utility item. They can be found in the store, under 4 different variations.</string>
    <string name="beacon_notes">Just like any other buyable item, they cannot be dropped or recycled.</string>

    <string name="badges_intro_header">About Badges in Ingress</string>
    <string name="badges_intro">Badges aren\'t important as long as you plan to stay at level 8 or below. But once you want to reach levels above level 8, you will need a certain amount of badges to be able to reach those levels. Other than that, badges don\'t have any function other than bragging rights.</string>
    <string name="badge_full_name">Badge name:</string>
    <string name="badge_image">Badge image:</string>
    <string name="badge_description">Description</string>
    <string name="badge_acquisition">How to get it</string>
    <string name="badge_versions">Stages/Levels</string>
    <string name="badge_notes">Notes</string>
    <string name="item_intro">Items are a big part of the game.</string>
    <string name="connection_error">Connection error!</string>
    <string name="xml_error">XML Error!</string>
    <string name="badge_variations_bronze">-bronze</string>
    <string name="badge_variations_full">-bronze\n-silver\n-gold\n-platinum\n-onyx</string>
    <string name="item_acquisition_playing">-via playing</string>

    <string name="abaddon">Abaddon</string>
    <string name="abaddon_description">The Abaddon Anomaly Badge was awarded only to people who made a contribution on the Abaddon Anomaly series, either as a field-agent or remote intel agent. In order to receive one of these, you had to register on the official Niantic Event.</string>
    <string name="abaddon_notes">You were able to get this badge when contributing to one of the following events:
    \n\n14th November 2015:
    \nHamburg, Germany (P)
    \nEdinburgh, UK (S)
    \nSeville, Spain (S)
    \nZagreb, Croatia (S)
    \n\nNew Orleans, USA (P)
    \nCharlotte, USA (S)
    \nGuatemala City, Guatemala (S)
    \nPittsburgh, USA (S)
    \n\nNew Taipei City (P)
    \nBangkok, Thailand (S)
    \nManila, Philippines (S)
    \nSydney, Australia (S)
    \n\n12th December 2015:
    \nOakland, USA (P)
    \nFort Worth, USA
    \nLima, Peru (S)
    \nPhoenix, USA (S)
    \n\nOkinawa, Japan (P)
    \nSeoul, South Korea (S)
    \nSingapore, Singapore (S)
    \nWellington, New Zealand (S)
    \n\nMilan, Italy (P)
    \nGdansk, Poland (S)
    \nPorto, Portugal (S)
    \nSofia, Bulgaria (S) </string>

    <string name="darsana">Darsana</string>
    <string name="darsana_description">The Darsana Anomaly Badge was awarded only to people who made a contribution on the Darsana Anomaly series, either as a field-agent or remote intel agent. In order to receive one of these, you had to register on the official Niantic Event.</string>
    <string name="darsana_notes">You were able to get this badge when contributing to one of the following events:
    \n\n28th October 2014:
    \nBrussels, Belgium (P)
    \nAarhus, Denmark (S)
    \nBerne, Switzerland (S)
    \nVilnius, Lithuania (S)
    \nPune, India (S)
    \n\nSalt Lake City, Utah, USA (P)
    \nAnchorage, Alaska, USA (S)
    \nHonolulu, Hawaii, USA (S)
    \n\n15th November 2014:
    \nNew Orleans, Louisiana, USA (P)
    \nOklahoma City, Oklahoma, USA (S)
    \nSanto Domingo, Dominican Republic (S)
    \nVirginia Beach, Virginia, USA (S)
    \n\n13th December 2014:
    \nTokyo, Japan(P)
    \nAuckland, New Zealand (S)
    \nManila, Philippines(S)
    \nSeoul, Korea (S)
    \n\nBarcelona, Spain (P)
    \nPretoria, South Africa (S)
    \nStuttgart, Germany (S)
    \nToulouse, France (S)
    \n\nCharleston, South Carolina, USA (P)
    \nHartford, Connecticut, USA (S)
    \nRio de Janeiro, Brazil (S)
    \nSanta Cruz, California, USA (S) </string>

    <string name="helios">Helios</string>
    <string name="helios_description">The Helios Anomaly Badge was awarded only to people who made a contribution on the Helios Anomaly series, either as a field-agent or remote intel agent. In order to receive one of these, you had to register on the official Niantic Event.</string>
    <string name="helios_notes">You were able to get this badge when contributing to one of the following events:
    \n\n12th July 2014:
    \nMontreal, Quebec, Canada (P)
    \nChattanooga, Tennessee, USA (S)
    \nToronto, Ontario, Canada (S)
    \n\n26th July 2014:
    \nSan Diego, California, USA (P)
    \nPhiladelphia, Pennsylvania, USA (S)
    \nBoston, Massachusetts, USA (S)
    \n\nDublin, Ireland (P)
    \nTallinn, Estonia (S)
    \nPalermo, Italy (S)
    \n\n9th August 2014:
    \nChicago, Illinois, USA (P)
    \nRichmond, Virginia, USA (S)
    \nGalveston, Texas, USA (S)
    \n\nTaipei (P)
    \nHong Kong, China (S)
    \nKuala Lumpur, Malaysia (S)
    \n\n23rd August 2014:
    \nDetroit, Michigan, USA (P)
    \nBaltimore, Maryland, USA (S)
    \nIndianapolis, Indiana, USA (S)
    \n\nPrague, Czech Republic (P)
    \nManchester, United Kingdom (S)
    \nRotterdam, The Netherlands (S)
    \n\n6th September 2014:
    \nMinneapolis, Minnesota, USA (P)
    \nTulsa, Oklahoma, USA (S)
    \nMonterrey, Mexico (S)
    \n\nBogota, Colombia (P)
    \nAsuncion, Paraguay (S)
    \nBuenos Aires, Argentina (S)
    \n\n24th September 2014:
    \nLondon, United Kingdom (Special Edition)
    \n\n27th September 2014:
    \nTacoma, Washington, USA (P)
    \nSacramento, California, USA (S)
    \nVancouver, British Columbia, Canada (S)
    \n\nMunich, Germany (P)
    \nGothenburg, Sweden (S)
    \nRiga, Latvia (S) </string>

    <string name="interitus">Helios</string>
    <string name="interitus_description">The Interitus Anomaly Badge was awarded only to people who made a contribution on the Interitus Anomaly series, either as a field-agent or remote intel agent. In order to receive one of these, you had to register on the official Niantic Event.</string>
    <string name="interitus_notes">You were able to get this badge when contributing to one of the following events:
    \n\n12th April 2014:
    \nAmsterdam, The Netherlands (P)
    \nGlasgow, United Kingdom (S)
    \nMalaga, Spain (S)
    \n\n26th April 2014
    \nLondon, United Kingdom (P)
    \nFlagstaff, Arizona, USA (P)
    \nFrankfurt, Germany (S)
    \nStockholm, Sweden (S)
    \nColorado Springs, Colorado, USA (S)
    \nSalt Lake City, Utah, USA (S)
    \n\n10th May 2014
    \nIshinomaki, Japan (P)
    \nSanta Fe, New Mexico (P)
    \nBeijing, China (S)
    \nSeoul, South Korea (S)
    \nHelena, Montana (S)
    \nMadison, Alabama (S)
    \n\n17th May 2014
    \nMelbourne, Australia (P)
    \nKansas City, Missouri (P)
    \nAuckland, New Zealand (S)
    \nBrisbane, Australia (S)
    \nCheyenne, Wyoming, USA (S)
    \nSioux Falls, South Dakota (S)
    \n\n7th June 2014
    \nSantiago, Chile (P)
    \nCincinnati, Ohio (P)
    \nSan Jose, California, USA (S)
    \nSan Juan, Puerto Rico (S)
    \nAsheville, North Carolina (S)
    \nBirmingham, England (S)
    \n\n21st June 2014:
    \nKrakow, Poland (P)
    \nGettysburg, Pennsylvania (P)
    \nBergen, Norway (S)
    \nSt Petersburg, Russia(S)
    \nHoboken, New Jersey (S)
    \nJacksonville, Florida, USA (S)</string>

    <string name="persepolis">Persepolis</string>
    <string name="persepolis_description">The Persepolis Anomaly Badge was awarded only to people who made a contribution on the Persepolis Anomaly series, either as a field-agent or remote intel agent. In order to receive one of these, you had to register on the official Niantic Event.</string>
    <string name="persepolis_notes">You were able to get this badge when contributing to one of the following events:
    \n\n30th May 2015:
    \nBratislava, Slovakia (P)
    \nCovilhã, Portugal (S)
    \nThessaloniki, Greece (S)
    \nBari, Italy (S)
    \n\nWashington, District of Columbia, USA (P)
    \nPhoenix, Arizona, USA (S)
    \nToronto, Canada (S)
    \nBuenos Aires, Argentina (S)
    \n\n20th June 2015:
    \nUtrecht, The Netherlands (P)
    \nLiverpool, United Kingdom (S)
    \nPoznan, Poland (S)
    \nHelsinki, Finland (S)
    \n\nTohoku, Japan (P)
    \nJakarta, Indonesia (S)
    \nPerth, Australia (S)
    \n\nPortland, Oregon, USA (P)
    \nMilwaukee, Wisconsin, USA (S)
    \nNashville, Tennessee, USA (S)
    \nFt Collins, Colorado, USA (S) </string>

    <string name="shonin">Shōnin</string>
    <string name="shonin_description">The Shōnin Anomaly Badge was awarded only to people who made a contribution on the Shōnin Anomaly series, either as a field-agent or remote intel agent. In order to receive one of these, you had to register on the official Niantic Event.</string>
    <string name="shonin_notes">You were able to get this badge when contributing to one of the following events:
    \n\n21st February 2015:
    \nAustin, Texas, USA (P)
    \nLas Vegas, Nevada, USA (S)
    \nAtlanta, Georgia, USA (S)
    \nMedellin, Colombia (S)
    \n\nFlorence, Italy (P)
    \nBrno, Czech Republic (S)
    \nAlexandria, Egypt (S)
    \nBilbao, Spain (S)
    \n\n28th March 2015:
    \nPasadena, California, USA (P)
    \nLima, Peru (S)
    \nDenver, Colorado, USA (S)
    \nOrlando, Florida, USA (S)
    \n\nHanover, Germany (P)
    \nCardiff, United Kingdom (S)
    \nReykjavik, Iceland (S)
    \nYekaterinburg, Russia (S)
    \n\nKyoto, Japan (P)
    \nAdelaide, Australia (S)
    \nChristchurch, New Zealand (S)
    \nGuangzhou, China (S) </string>


    <string name="builder_description">To get the Builder medal, you need to deploy or upgrade resonators</string>
    <string name="builder_notes">The different stages of the Builder medal:\nBronze: 2.000\nSilver: 10.000\nGold: 30.000\nPlatinum: 100.000\nOnyx: 200.000</string>

    <string name="connector_description">To get the Connector medal, you need to establish portal links.</string>
    <string name="connector_notes">The different stages of the Connector medal:\nBronze: 50\nSilver: 1.000\nGold: 5.000\nPlatinum: 25.000\nOnyx: 100.000</string>

    <string name="engineer_description">To get the Engineer medal, you need to deploy mods.</string>
    <string name="engineer_notes">The different stages of the Engineer medal:\nBronze: 150\nSilver: 1.500\nGold: 5.000\nPlatinum: 20.000\nOnyx: 50.000</string>

    <string name="explorer_description">To get the Explorer medal, you need to visit portals. By "visiting" is meant upgrading, either by deploying mods and resonators or by hacking (easiest method), but also by linking. Basically every action on a portal counts as a visit.</string>
    <string name="explorer_notes">The different stages of the Engineer medal:\nBronze: 100\nSilver: 1.000\nGold: 2.000\nPlatinum: 10.000\nOnyx: 30.000</string>

    <string name="hacker_description">To get the Hacker medal, you need to hack portals.</string>
    <string name="hacker_notes">The different stages of the Hacker medal:\nBronze: 2.000\nSilver 10.000\nGold: 30.0000\nPlatinum: 100.000\nOnyx: 200.000</string>

    <string name="illuminator_description">To get the Illuminator medal, you need to capture MU by creating control fields. </string>
    <string name="illuminator_notes">The different stages of the Builder medal:\nBronze: 5.000\nSilver: 50.000\nGold: 250.000\nPlatinum: 1.000.000\nOnyx: 4.000.000</string>

    <string name="liberator_description">To get the Liberator medal, you need to simply capture portals.</string>
    <string name="liberator_notes">The different stages of the Liberator medal:\nBronze: 100\nSilver: 1.000\nGold: 5.000\nPlatinum: 15.000\nOnyx: 40.000</string>

    <string name="mindcontroller_description">To get the Mind Controller medal, you need make fields.</string>
    <string name="mindcontroller_notes">The different stages of the Mind Controller medal:\nBronze: 100\nSilver: 500\nGold: 2.000\nPlatinum: 10.000\nOnyx: 40.000</string>

    <string name="purifier_description">To get the Purifier medal, you need to destroy resonators with XMPs.</string>
    <string name="purifier_notes">The different stages of the Purifier medal:\nBronze: 2.000\nSilver: 10.000\nGold: 30.000\nPlatinum: 100.000\nOnyx: 300.000</string>

    <string name="recharger_description">To get the Recharger medal, you need to recharge portals. This can be done by going into your inventory, selecting \"Portal keys\" and recharging any portal that isn\'t fully charged yet.</string>
    <string name="recharger_notes">The different stages of the Recharger medal:\nBronze: 100.000\nSilver: 1.000.000\nGold: 300.000\nPlatinum: 10.000.000\nOnyx: 25.000.000</string>

    <string name="sojourner_description">To get the Sojourner medal, you need to hack any portal in a period of 24 hours, for a given time.</string>
    <string name="sojourner_notes">The different stages of the Sojourner medal:\nBronze: 15\nSilver: 30\nGold: 60\nPlatinum: 180\nOnyx: 360</string>

    <string name="specops_description">To get the Specops medal, you need to complete missions. Missions can be found in the "Missions"-tab in Ingress (pretty obvious) and are sorted by rating and distance of the mission-beginning portal to you.</string>
    <string name="specops_notes">The different stages of the Specops medal:\nBronze: 5\nSilver: 25\nGold: 100\nPlatinum: 200\nOnyx: 500</string>

    <string name="translator_description">To get the Translator medal, you need to perform glyph hacks instead of normal hacks. Glyphs can done by pressing and holding the "Hack Portal" Button when in range of a portal. The game of glyphing is the following: You will be shown 1 to 5 patterns (depending on the portals level) which you have to remind. After the patterns being shown, you have to redo them. You can get up to 15 glyph points when succeeding in a level 8 portal glyph hack.</string>
    <string name="translator_notes">The different stages of the Translator medal:\nBronze: 200\nSilver: 2.000\nGold: 6.000\nPlatinum: 20.000\nOnyx: 50.000</string>

    <string name="trekker_description">To get the Trekker medal, you need to move around. A lot.</string>
    <string name="trekker_notes">The different stages of the Trekker medal:\nBronze: 10\nSilver: 100\nGold: 300\nPlatinum: 10.000\nOnyx: 2.500</string>


    <string name="aided_ada">Aided Ada</string>
    <string name="aided_ada_description">Ada is the name of a character in the storyline. You were able to get this badge at an event where Ada was present.</string>
    <string name="aided_ada_notes">You are not able to receive this badge anymore, unless you have a valid passcode.</string>

    <string name="eve">Eve</string>
    <string name="eve_description">The EVE Medal is similar to the Recruiter medal. It was introduced in July 2014 and to get it, agents had to recruit at least 3 more agents in a timespan of 20 days. Another difference to the Recruiter badge: You\'ve only received the EVE badge when recruiting iPhone agents.</string>
    <string name="eve_notes">As mentioned previously, you are not able to get this badge anymore.</string>

    <string name="founder">Founder</string>
    <string name="founder_description">The Founder badge is one of the oldest, non-tiered badges. Players received this badge in recognition of their contribution during the early days of Ingress. To get this badge, agents had to be Level 5 or more at December 14th 2013.</string>
    <string name="founder_notes">You can not get this badge anymore. That\'s why the players who own it since the beginning of Ingress are very proud of it.</string>

    <string name="hankjohnson">Hank Johnson</string>
    <string name="hankjohnson_description">For this badge you had to meet Hank Johnson, although this fact is unconfirmed. You were able to meet him at the Shōnin anomaly in Hannover, Germany in March 28th 2015.</string>
    <string name="hankjohnson_notes"> </string>

    <string name="initio">Initio</string>
    <string name="initio_description">The Initio Badge was awarded only to people who bought a t-shirt during the Interitus Anomaly series. </string>
    <string name="initio_notes">You are not able to get this badge, unless you have a valid passcode.</string>

    <string name="innovator">Innovator</string>
    <string name="innovator_description">The Innovator badge is the second Founder. It has been released on November 15th 2014, to every player with at least level 3. It rewards the players which have made a contribution during the first 2 years with a good looking medal.</string>
    <string name="innovator_notes">The different stages of the Innovator medal are:
    \n\nBronze: Level 3\nSilver: Level 9\nGold: Level 11\nPlatinum: Level 13\nOnyx (Black): Level 15</string>

    <string name="missionday">Mission Day</string>
    <string name="missionday_description">The Mission Day badge is earned by contributing to a specified amount of special missions on an official Mission Day. These missions are mostly done in a group of people. The Mission Day medal can be gained after every anomaly in will stay the same.</string>
    <string name="missionday_notes"> </string>

    <string name="nl1331">NL-1331</string>
    <string name="nl1331_description">What is it all about those NL-1331 badges? Where do people get them from?\n This badge can only be acquired when being at the right time at the right spot. A special van of the NIA group may come to your town and hand them out.</string>
    <string name="nl1331_notes">Unfortunately we have no idea if this badge is still available. Sure that on ebay or other online markets you may buy them, but there is no information of another visit of the NIA van.</string>
    <!--Add image NIA van-->

    <string name="stellavyctory">Stella Vyctory</string>
    <string name="stellavyctory_description">Stella Vyctory is a character in Ingress like Hank Johnson. This badge bas distributed at the Hanover anomaly (Shonin) to people who chose a line. </string>
    <string name="stellavyctory_notes">As many other badges, you can not get this badge anymore unless you find a valid passcode.</string>

    <string name="susannamoyer">Susanna Moyer</string>
    <string name="susannamoyer_description">Susanna Moyer is the main investigative journalist. She appears in almost every Media reports and emails from Ingress. Since there is so much about her, see this link for more, detailed information: https://niantic.schlarp.com/investigation:characters:susanna_moyer</string>
    <string name="susannamoyer_notes">As many other badges, you can not get this badge anymore unless you find a valid passcode.</string>

    <string name="vanguard">Vanguard</string>
    <string name="vanguard_description">The Vanguard badge was awarded only to people who reached at least level 3 at the 1st December 2015. It is to reward people for playing Ingress in year 3. </string>
    <string name="vanguard_notes">The different stages of the Innovator medal are:
    \n\nBronze: Level 3\nSilver: Level 9\nGold: Level 13\nPlatinum: Level 15\nOnyx (Black): Level 16\n\n As you may have recognised, this medal has higher ranks than its previous one, the Innovator.</string>

    <string name="verified">Verified</string>
    <string name="verified_description">When you reach level 2 you\'ll be asked to enter a verification code that will be sent to you via SMS to verify that you are, in fact, you. Once that\'s done you\'ll automatically get the \'Verified\' badge and your inventory space will be expanded from 200 to 2000 items.</string>
    <string name="verified_notes"> </string>

    <string name="action_submit_faq">Submit Question</string>
    <string name="submit_a_question">Question Submission</string>
    <string name="choose_email_app">Choose email client</string>
    <string name="question_submission_email">faq.guide@colinries.com</string>
    <string name="support_email">support@colinries.com</string>
    <string name="guide_support">Support (Guide)</string>
    <string name="feedback_email">feedback@colinries.com</string>
    <string name="guide_feedback">Feedback (Guide)</string>
    <string name="unlockPortalSim">Unlock Portal Sim</string>
    <string name="donateS">Donate S</string>
    <string name="donateM">Donate M</string>
    <string name="donateL">Donate L</string>
    <string name="thankyou">Thank You!</string>
    <string name="purchasecancelled">Purchase cancelled!</string>
    <string name="premiumunlocked">Premium Unlocked!</string>
    <string name="premiumunlockneeded">Premium Needed!</string>
    <string name="buy">Buy!</string>
    <string name="nothanks">No Thanks!</string>
    <string name="purchasefailed">Purchase Failed!</string>
    <string name="error">Error!</string>
    <string name="errorconsumingitem">Error Consuming Item!</string>
    <string name="dialogpremiuminfo">You can use the Portal Simulator to simulate different portal configurations and get information like energy, link range… This feature is a premium feature. When you decide to unlock this feature, you\'ll also have every future premium feature that we\'ll release.</string>

</resources>
